papajohns.co.uk 2019-12-16

# Pizza Delivery | Order Quality Pizza Online With Papa John's

Papa John's (GB) Limited (trading as Papa John's) has created this Privacy Notice in order to demonstrate our strong commitment to protecting the privacy of all visitors to our site. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, they can be directed to [dataprotection@papajohns.co.uk](mailto:dataprotection@papajohns.co.uk) or in writing to the address supplied at the bottom of this page.

### Part One: All visitors to [www.papajohns.co.uk](https://www.papajohns.co.uk/) are promised that:

  * Papa John's will always respect your right to privacy. However, we understand that the internet is not a secure medium and therefore we have implemented security measures to, where possible, protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information placed under our control.
  * All data gathered as a result of your website visit or visit to our stores will be treated as confidential.
  * All orders placed online will be confirmed by email if you have provided an email address.

### Part Two: How we use your data

  * To place an order, enter a promotion or take part in an online survey, you will be required to supply contact and personal information.
  * For our 'customers', we use your personal data for certain legitimate business purposes, for example we may ask for your name, address, phone number and email, to tell you about new products and services and to send you marketing communication and offers to use in stores or on our website. We may also send you surveys to help us improve how we service you.
  * We will consider you as a 'customer' for 13 months since the date of your last order. If you do not order within 13 months you will automatically be opted out of receiving our direct marketing.
  * If you order again from us after 13 months and have not opted out, we have a legitimate interest to re-commence sending you marketing communications about our products and services.
  * You can opt out of these messages at any time by going to your online account or by using our [unsubscribe page](https://www.papajohns.co.uk/unsubscribe.aspx).
  * We may use personal and profile data to tailor your experience on our interactive services.
  * We may use your IP address or other identifying information to help diagnose problems with our server, to monitor numbers of users and/or to administer our interactive services as well as to identify and eliminate fraud.
  * Accordingly, Papa John's would encourage you to be cautious about the information you choose to release and to safeguard passwords.
  * For people who have registered on our website but haven't yet bought any of our products and services, we will ask for your consent to process your data before we send you marketing offers.   
In order to process your order and subsequent communications there is a need for us to transfer some of your data outside of the EU. If at any point we transfer your personal data outside of the EU we will make sure the same level of protection is provided to your data and in line with the GDPR.
  * We will request that users who wish to submit personal information are aged 16 years or older or that minors obtain permissionfrom their parents or legal guardians before submitting such information.
  * Whenever we process your personal data for these purposes we will ensure that we always keep your personal data rights in high regard and take account of these rights. You have the right to object to this processing if you wish and if you wish to do so please contact us at [dataprotection@papajohns.co.uk](mailto:dataprotection@papajohns.co.uk). Please bear in mind that if you object this may affect our ability to carry out the tasks above for your benefit.

### Part Three: How long will you keep my data?

  * We'll normally hold onto your data if you're a customer, for as long as is necessary to give you the services you're using in accordance with our retention policy.
  * If you don't use our services or your Papa John's account for over 24 months then your account may be classified as dormant and may be deleted in line with our privacy notice and retention policy.
  * Please check your inbox to see if we've sent you any emails about this recently.

### Part Four: Your rights as a data subject

At any point while we are in possession of or processing your personal data, you, the data subject, have the following rights:

  * Right of access – you have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you.
  * Right of rectification – you have a right to correct data that we hold about you that is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * Right to be forgotten – in certain circumstances you can ask for the data we hold about you to be erased from our records.
  * Right to restriction of processing – where certain conditions apply to have a right to restrict the processing.
  * Right of portability – you have the right to have the data we hold about you transferred to another organisation.
  * Right to object – you have the right to object to certain types of processing such as direct marketing.

To get in touch, email: [dataprotection@papajohns.co.uk](mailto:dataprotection@papajohns.co.uk)

Or write to:   
Customer Services   
Papa John's   
11 Northfield Drive   
Milton Keynes   
MK15 0DQ   
Tel: 0203 6936800 

You may be asked for ID to confirm your identity.

### Part Five: Cookies

Currently cookies are used on www.papajohns.co.uk to identify you for usability purposes and to allow you to process your order throughout the website. For example, by remembering which store you have selected or your preference for delivery or collection. In addition, we may use 3rd party cookies to help improve your experience or to track the performance of our marketing programs. In all cases, your personal information is not stored in cookies.

For further information on cookies please refer to [https://cookiesandyou.com](https://cookiesandyou.com/).

This site includes instructions on how to accept or reject cookies and also how to remove them should you wish to do so.

### Part Six: Disclaimer

If Papa John's provides links to other services, Papa John's is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these services. Papa John's reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy notice at any time and you are therefore encouraged to review it from time to time.

### Part Seven: Trademarks and Copyright

All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, button icons, images and software, is the property of Papa John's and is protected by UK and European copyright laws. The content and software on this site may be used as either or both of an informational or shopping resource. Any other use, including the reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display or performance, of the content on this site is strictly prohibited. Other Papa John's graphics, logos and trade names are trademarks of Papa John's. Papa John's trademarks may not be used in connection with any product or service that is not affiliated with Papa John's in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers, or in any manner that disparages or discredits Papa John's.

### Part Eight: Terms and Conditions

Our Terms and Conditions can be viewed here from the link below.

### Part Nine: Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice or you wish to make a complaint about how your personal data is being processed by us, or how your complaint has been handled, you have the right to lodge a complaint directly with the Supervisory Authority and Papa John's data protection representative.

The details for the latter are:

Data Protection [(dataprotection@papajohns.co.uk)](mailto:dataprotection@papajohns.co.uk)   
Papa John's   
11 Northfield Drive   
Milton Keynes   
MK15 0DQ   
Tel: 0203 6936800 

### Changes to this notice

From time to time Papa John's may need to make changes to this Privacy Notice. Recent changes are shown below:

  * 22nd November 2019. Changed who created this Privacy Notice in the opening paragraph from Papa John's to Papa John’s (GB) Limited.
